The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Wan'er ?
Wan'er !
No !
It's him...
You still haven't found your soul strand ?
Perhaps you're fated to die here.
Burn !
Stop !
I can't let him harm Wan'er's soul strand.
It's you !
A Soul Flag ?
If you make one more move,
you're dead !
Damn it,
this place is collapsing.
I'll need to find another method to get my soul strand.
If this place collapses,
Wan'er's soul strand will die too.
Merge !
Thank you for your help, little friend.
My only way to find her soul strand
is to keep destroying the spirit's body.
You saved me
and then you attacked me.
What's wrong with you !?
Destroy !
Wan'er !
Where are you ?
Madman !
You're insane !
Destroy !
Wan'er !
Wan'er...
Don't be afraid.
Metal Souls' Basin
Suzaku Tomb
The collapse is accelerating.
I must find the central mountain,
reclaim my soul strand,
and then I escape this place.
This is...
Metal soul strands ?
Xu Liguo !
My grandkids,
don't you dare provoke your grandpa Xu !
Escaping ?
Did I say you could escape ?
A spirit formed from metal soul strands
resembles a Sword Spirit.
That means Xu Liguo can counter them.
This aura...
It's strikingly similar to a celestial sword.
Such powerful pressure !
This blade is made of a single soul strand, not multiple.
Swords have their pride
and blades have their fury.
This is no ordinary weapon.
I want
your Sword Spirit.
You
can leave.
No no no !
This blade is really fast,
the same speed as the 4th primary soul.
But its attacks are stronger.
Leave
him here !
Ceng Niu,
thanks to you distracting the metal soul strands,
I was able to pass safely.
Since that's the case,
I'll leave you a little gift.
Didn't you want a rematch with Ceng Niu ?
I'll give you that chance today.
Kill him.
This half-moon blade doesn't try to harm Xu Liguo.
Maybe it has other intentions ?
Xu Liguo,
bear with it
for a moment.
Master !
You can't !
A devil like you won't die easily.
Once I reclaim my soul strand,
I'll come back for you.
Don't you dare forget to save me !
This blade is a treasure.
When I come back for Xu Liguo,
I need to subdue it too.
Central spirit mountain outskirts
Suzaku Tomb
This must be the mountain.
Red Butterfly !
Qian Feng refined her into his cauldron
and she's lost her consciousness.
I don't have much time,
I have to deal with her fast.
Can you
kill me ?
She's still conscious !
I...
I can't
control myself.
I don't want
to live like this.
I beg you,
kill me !
I, Red Butterfly,
would rather die
than live in shame.
In my centuries of cultivation,
you were one of the few people
that I, Wang Lin, considered a rival.
I never imagined that our final battle
would end up like this.
I admire your pride and your spirit.
I will grant
your wish.
Do it.
Looking back at my youth,
I was the rising star of Xue Yue.
100 years to reach Soul Formation
but I was forever stuck at Soul Formation.
And now I'm a puppet
100 years to Soul Formation,
will I be remembered or forgotten ?
and have no hope of freedom.
My only way to be free
It doesn't matter who plays white or black,
the game is unpredictable.
is death.
All of the discarded pieces
are equally illusory.
I lived less than 200 years.
When the mind is empty and dies,
it forgets that the violence of the chessboard
Life is like a butterfly,
gone in an instant.
But that instant
was not in vain.
is unforgettable.
Farewell...
My past life's wounds are willing to become
a butterfly landing on your shoulder.
I will face this disaster and break my chains.
I will never give up my pride.
This is our karma,
my death was inevitable.
I seek my liberation this very moment.
Please remember me...
Qian Feng's domain
is endless desire.
He devours domains to understand them
and refine his own domain.
I leave you my insights of his domain and the Soul Lasher.
Ceng Niu,
help me.
Kill Qian Feng.
Please...
Next spring,
a blue rose will bloom
in the northern plains.
That is my gift to you.
I promise.
By using the Void Ancestor's Skull,
I'll open a passage to the Suzaku Tomb.
Only one person can enter
and time is limited.
If you don't exit before the tattoo fades,
you'll be erased.
Who goes ?
I will.
Once I find the Cultivation Planet Crystal,
I'll use a reverse formation to repair it
and prevent the arrival of the Cultivation Alliance.
I will protect our clan.
It will be dangerous,
be careful.
Come back safely.
Central spirit mountain entrance
Suzaku Tomb
Is this the place ?
Be patient, just a little longer.
How much longer exactly ?
Yunque Zi was able to breach the barrier and enter the tomb ?
Impossible...
That's right,
how did he do it ?
Greetings, Senior.
Senior,
Junior has been waiting for you.
This door
is impossible to open.
Don't worry,
this is the only path to the first Suzaku's tomb.
But it won't open without
the Cultivation Planet Crystal.
We need to wait a bit more for the collapse of the Suzaku Tomb
and the door will open,
allowing us to enter.
He's not from planet Suzaku...
Although he's Peak Late stage Soul Transformation,
I still have a strange feeling about him.
May I know which fellow cultivator possessed this body ?
Show me your true form.
We've never met.
Even if I reveal myself,
you won't know who I am.
Step back !
Stay away from the spatial rifts !
How did it start collapsing ?
The Suzaku Tomb
has almost completely collapsed.
That Zi Xin bitch !
He's still not here...
Ceng Niu,
I hope Heartless sent you off to hell.
Brother Wang !
Ceng Niu !
Wang Lin...
We're finally reaching
the climax of the game.
To let go of the consequences of my actions
is to ignore the law of cause and effect
like scattered ink.
As destiny falls
in exchange for this moment of tainted dreams.
It makes the mountains lose their colors,
wither and melt into rivers.
Who can deceive
the law of the heavens ?
Countless generations
have tried before me.
But how could I not catch my dreams
within my warm fingers ?
You're at my side when I'm alone
giving me the strength to fight the will of the heavens.
Fortunately, my mind was open and honest.
I'm sorry we never got to see the fireworks
in the streets.
Can I break the vortex of our destiny ?
Can I break the rules ?
To run towards you !
I will fight the law of the heavens and the law of cause and effect
to cut down this tribulation with my own hands
and break through the reincarnation cycle.
All of that for the stars in your eyes.
I wish to bend this dream for the fire in my heart.
If your soul is willing to wander,
can I still take your hands
and hold them tight ?
I will defy the heavens and prevent the stars from falling.
I will overthrow the Immortals and the Demons in my heart.
I dream of destroying
the shackles of our fate.
You're the only one that can ignore the law of cause and effect.
You're the hardest to let go of.
I want to be with you again
so I can look in your eyes.
Even for a moment, it's worth it.